ayearwithmomanddad.com 2014-11-22

# Disclosures & Privacy Policies

**_DISCLOSURE_**

_This policy is valid from 15 June 2010._

_This blog is a collaborative blog written by a group of individuals (Mom & Dad!). For questions about this blog, please contact Julie (Jkrs01 at Comcast.net)._

_This blog accepts forms of cash advertising, sponsorship, paid insertions or other forms of compensation. We will and do accept and keep free products, services, travel, event tickets, and other forms of compensation from companies and organizations._

_This blog abides by word of mouth marketing standards. We believe in honesty of relationship, opinion and identity. The compensation received may influence the advertising content, topics or posts made in this blog. That content, advertising space or post will be clearly identified as paid or sponsored content._

_The owner(s) of this blog is compensated to provide opinion on products, services, websites and various other topics. Even though the owner(s) of this blog receives compensation for our posts or advertisements, we always give our honest opinions, findings, beliefs, or experiences on those topics or products. The views and opinions expressed on this blog are purely the bloggers’ own. Any product claim, statistic, quote or other representation about a product or service should be verified with the manufacturer, provider or party in question._

_This blog does not contain any content which might present a conflict of interest._

_To get your own policy, go to<http://www.disclosurepolicy.org/>_

**PRIVACY POLICY:**

This policy is valid from May 1, 2011

A Year With Mom and Dad respects your privacy.

A Year With Mom and Dad and its affiliates may use cookies to store information about your preferences and other information. Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and A Year With Mom and Dad does not use cookies to collect personal information. Cookies may also be used by 3rd party content providers. Some advertising partners may use cookies. Some of the partners include, but not limited to Groupon, Ebates, and others. A Year With Mom and Dad is not responsible for information obtained from affiliates.

To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice visit the NAI at [http://www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/). To opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.aboutads.info/choices>.

A Year With Mom and Dad is not responsible for the content of external internet sites. You are advised to read the privacy policy of external sites before disclosing any personal information.

A Year With Mom and Dad may on occasion ask for personal information, such as for giveaways. This information will not be sold or used for any purpose other than contacting the winner of the giveaway. Your information may be sent to giveaway providers for mailing the giveaway. A Year With Mom and Dad is not responsible for information shared with giveaway sponsors as a means of mailing a giveaway. It is the intent of A Year With Mom and Dad that this information be colleted for confirming winners of a giveaway as a method of prize distribution only.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>
